hello
здравствуйте
Good afternoon I'm from the city of Khmelnitsky Where are you
Добрый день Я из города Хмельницкий А вы
from
откуда
Nizhny Novgorod Nizhny Novgorod I understand
Нижний Новгород Нижний Новгород понял
how you have a holiday there today and what
как у вас там сегодня с праздничком а
holiday is the day of the drop-dead blow
праздник какой день офигительного удара
to Sevastopol just saying to the headquarters of the
по севастополю просто кая по штабу
Black Sea Fleet
Черноморского флота
it's just a thrill just a year and a half
просто это кайф просто полтора года
of its life
своего
How about the fact that this is a historical
Как насчет того что это историческое
building
здание
Yes, unfortunately, about 15 historians there
Да к сожалению там около 15 историков
died, the
погибло
chief doctor Nau of some kind, they closed their eyes,
главный доктор Нау какого-то зажмурили
there were also a dozen candidates and so
еще там десяток кандидатов и так
a few graduate students
аспирантов немножко
You say that this is Ukraine, this is
Вы же говорить что это Украина это
occupied Ukraine Yes, also
Украина оккупированная Да также
Wait, it was occupied before,
Подождите оккупированная она была раньше
now
сейчас
liberation is taking place, so this is the process of
происходит освобождение вот так процесс
driving vehicles,
средств вождения
we seem to  we have a lot of simple things in
мы как бы у нас очень много просто в
Ukraine, lately a lot of
Украине последнее время очень много
people have become interested in history, it’s
людей стало интересоваться историей вот
just that we have an exchange of experience between our
просто вот у нас обмен опытом нашей
historians and your grandfathers. Our historians
историки с вашими дед Вот наши историки
sent a dissertation, for example,
до послали диссертацию например
from your face I see that you are also
по вашему лицу вижу что вы тоже
filled with the happiness of joy, you can
исполнены знаете счастьями радости вот
clearly see the radiance of yours  the smile doesn’t
прям видно сияние ваших глазах улыбка не
go away in my eyes, I do
сходит
n’t know, just in short,
не знаю просто короче
because you understand correctly internally, yes,
потому что правильно вы внутренне
that the liberation of Crimea before
понимаете да Что освобождение Крыма до
will give the key to the fall of this
даст ключ к падению вот этого
Putiller regime. Yes, and you will breathe
путиллеровского режима Да и вы вдохнете
in Nizhny Novgorod, you will breathe
в Нижнем Новгороде вздохнете на полной
deeply, your independent Nizhny Novgorod
груди свои независимые Нижегородской
Republic. So everything will be fine, man,
Республики Так что все будет хорошо
I’m just  I’m having a blast now it’s real,
я просто кайфую сейчас реально
it’s so yellow and blue everywhere, there are
это везде так желтые и синий других
no other colors. There are also red and black, but
цветов нет Есть еще красные и черный но
red black is kind of bad,
красный черный какой-то там нехороший
something is good, Bandera’s is good,
что-то там хороший бандеровский хороший
very good,
очень хороший
but Bandera’s people did nothing, they
да а бандеровцы ничего делали то они еще
weren’t mainstream yet,
не было мейнстримом
they’re
они
not only  some Buryats
не только еще и бурятов некоторые
came here
приходили сюда
before all sorts of people were in the Soviet Army whoever
были до всякие были Советской Армии кого
you want by the way Buryats since
хочешь кстати бурятов еще с
[music]
[музыка]
and where is Khatyn
а где находится хатынь
Khatyn in Belarus Belarus so And what does
хатынь в Белоруссии Белоруссии так А
Ukraine have to do with it a That’s because she
причем тут Украина а Вот потому что она
killed there
там убивала
you can go into detail Ukraine killed in
можно подетали Украина убивала в
Belarus but
Беларуси да
I don’t  I remember now what the regiment is called there,
я не помню Сейчас как там называется
but it’s called 118
полк но Называется он 118
118, not Bandera’s, no, not Bandera’s,
118 не бандеровский нет ни бандеровский
not some kind. It’s purely
не какой-то Там чисто
German-fascist, I don’t remember what it’s called,
немецко-фашистские не помню называется
but they
но
showed exactly what
показывали именно то что
your brothers, the Ukrainians, killed together with
ваши братья украинцы убивали вместе с
the Lithuanians, by the way,
литовцами кстати убивали
the Belarusians killed like that,
белорусы так
you’ve never heard of this
Вы не слышали никогда
I heard  Katyn you know this cats Khatyn
Я слышал Катынь такое знаете коты хатынь
is not Khatyn and cats you don’t know cats I don’t
это не хатынь а коты не знаете коты не
know where they shot Polish
знаю да где расстреляли польских
officers around 2000
офицеров около 2000
and you heard
а Вы слышали
when the Soviet Union together with
когда Советский Союз вместе с
Hitler’s Germany attacked Poland
гитлеровский Германии напали на Польшу
not quite like that, well, not really cats
не совсем так ну как не совсем в коты
shot prisoners of war
никого расстреляли военнопленных
Polish officers well  I wasn’t there I can’t
польских офицеров ну я там не был не
say in cats don’t go look
могу сказать в коты не зайди посмотри
it’s generally known
это вообще известный
Where did Polish prisoners of war come from in the Soviet Union in 1939
Откуда в Советском Союза В тридцать
September 1, 1939
1 сентября 39 года
German Germany
немецкая Германия
attacked Poland
напала на Польшу
gouged gouged gouged Poles
раздолбали раздолбали раздолбали поляк
you Soviet troops entered the former
ты советские войска вошли на бывшие
territories of
территории
Poland and how is it  former if there was
Польши и как это бывший если там было
a flood If the Germans had not yet captured it,
польнуло Если немцы еще не захватили не
but the fact is that it was Belarus
но дело в том что это была Беларуси
once again once again What kind of Belarus Belarus
еще раз еще раз Какая Беларуси Беларуси
was after 20 years When
была после 20 года Когда
Poland Germany attacked Poland so it
Польша Германия напала на Польшу так это
was Belarus in
было Беларуси
the ninth year it was the territory of Poland
девятом году это была территория Польши
after
после
not after
не после
Kamenny  century, yes, for example, the city of
Каменном веке еще да вот например город
Lviv. For example, the city Where did you run away,
Львов Вот например город Куда ты убежал
[ __ ]
говнюк
[music]
[музыка]
YouTube, driving us through the cardio
YouTube загоняя нас через кардиорке в
box into a shadow ban and even the richest looking one is not
теневый бан и дуже богатого вида не
shown to people in private;
показывается людям в частном на
information about streams is shown
показывается информация про стримы тому
in order for the slow-moving zazok
для того чтобы мало оперативный зазок
to subscribe right at once  and there are attempts there in a
подпишется прям за раз а попыт там в
kilogram about Krim video
килограмме о Крим видео
information and we are with you athermats on
информация и мы с вами атерматы по
stylish
стильной
operational stars laid down this will show
оперативной звездок заложено это покажем
you the YouTube word to Ukraine
вам YouTube слово Украине